参透你的交易逻辑并执行
and mirror your own trade logic in its executions.
在阿克斯资本我们尊重多元化的文化
At Axe Capital, we support people from all cultures,
但你跟我说话时  最好用该死的英语
but when you talk to me, it better be in fucking English.
我可以对泰勒的交易模式做个模型
I can model Taylor's trading patterns.
以十倍速
Reproduce them.
重现他们
At ten times the speed.
我的交易模式并不完美
My trading patterns are imperfect.
你的模式很棒
They're pretty fucking good.
是  但我不想要个很好用的算法
Yes, but I don't want a pretty fucking good algo.
-我一直就这意思  -这只是基础的东西
- That's what I've been saying. - No, but I start from there.
你会通过机器学习来模仿
The way that you would imitate Taylor's brain
-泰勒的大脑  -差不多  准确说是建模
-is by studying it, right? -Yes, modeling, as I said.